http://www.sdhqoffroad.com/pages/sdhq-privacy-policy

SDHQ Privacy Policy-SDHQ
HomeBrandsShop By Category Most Popular SuspensionLightingWheelsTiresSDHQ Built ProductsSDHQ Built Products Coming SoonSDHQ SwagSDHQ Stickers and DecalsAir Systems ARB Air SystemsOasis ManufacturingPowerTankVibrant Performance Air FiltersBed Accessories SDHQ Built In Bed Chase RacksDeckedBAKflip Bed CoversFront RunnerRetrax Bed CoversTransfer FlowWilco OffroadAMP ResearchBuiltRight IndustriesBumpers ARB BumpersCBI Off Road FabricationCamburg Engineering CTE Series BumpersICON Vehicle Dynamics | Impact Series Off-Road ArmorFab FoursWarn IndustriesCommunication PCI RadiosPCI RadiosPCI Race RadiosPCI Radio HeadsetsPCI RadiosPCI Radios | Lowrance GPS SystemssBullet Proof Diesel Antenna MountsCravenSpeedDrivetrain SDHQ Built Direct Replacement CV Boot KitsARB Air LockersNitro Gear and AxlesEaton Electrically-Actuated Locking DifferentialsDynatracLubelockerRCV PerformanceSDHQ Built CV Axle Boots and PartsElectrical Switch Pros SP9100 8-Switch Panel Power SystemBattery BoxesBullet Proof Diesel Antenna MountsDashlink OBDII Digital Gauges Apple iOS/AndroidSwitch ProsSDHQ Built Electrical ProductsBaja Designs Wiring HarnessesDC Power EngineeringRange TechnologySuperChipsExpedition Accessories ARBCamburg Engineering CTE Series CBI Off Road FabricationFreespirit RecreationFront RunnerGoose GearRCI Off RoadPrinsu DesignsTrail GearWilco OffroadBuiltRight IndustriesFabrication Parts SDHQ Built Fabrication ProductsBattery BoxesBallastic Fabrication Fabrication PartsCamburg Engineering Fabrication PartsFK Rod EndsFragola Performance SystemsAeromotive IncAeromotive | Fuel FiltersAeromotive | Fuel PumpsAeromotive | Fuel FittingsAeromotive | RegulatorsVibrant PerformanceVibrant | Titanium ProductsVibrant | TubingVibrant | Fluid DeliveryVibrant | FlangesVibrant | Air FiltersVibrant | Hoses and ClampsFiberglass SDHQ Built FiberglassFiberwerx Offroad FiberglassFuel Systems Aeromotive Inc.Holley EFI Products (Fuel Injection) S&B TanksTransfer Flow In Bed Fuel TanksRotopax ContainersRotopax | 2 Gallon Gasoline Gen 2 ContainerFuel Dump CansHunsaker Fuel Dump CansCB-IndustriesHolley Performance Fuel JugsUtility Jug w/ Filler HoseFuel Jug Filler HoseBattery Operated Transfer PumpMr. Gasket Fast Fill FunnelOils and AdditivesSwepco Lubrication SolutionsEvans CoolantRed Line Oil5.3 Gallon (20 Liter) Jerry CanInterior Accessories SDHQ Built Interior ProductsSDHQ Built Switch Pros MountsBuiltRight IndustriesBedside Rack SystemsDash Mount KitsVelcro Tech PanelsSwitch ProsPCI Race RadiosMPI Steering WheelsTuffy Security ProductsMob ArmorGoose GearXG CargoPutco LightingB&M PerformanceLighting Baja DesignsRigid IndustriesVision XPutco LightingSDHQ Built Lighting MountsSDHQ Built Billet Chase Light Mounting KitSDHQ Built Behind the Grille MountsSDHQ Built A-Pillar MountsSDHQ Switch Pros MountsLED Light BarsBaja Designs | LED Light BarsRigid Industries LED LightsVision X | LED Light BarsLED Auxiliary LightsBaja Designs | Auxiliary LightsRigid Industries | Auxiliary LED LightsVision X | Auxiliary LED LightsLED Rock LightsBaja Designs Rock and Dome LED LightsVision X | XP Series Rock LightsRigid A-Series Pro Rock Light LED Light KitOil, Additives and Cleaners Steel-It 1012B Black Polyurethane AerosolSteel-It 1002 Polyurethane Anti-Rust AerosolCleaners and Hand SanitizersLucas Oil Hand Sanitizer 2qt-11175Evans CoolantSwepco lubricants Red Line Oils Steel It SDIRevlock Race SuppliesPerformance aFe PerformanceDC Power EngineeringHolley PerformanceFlowmasterKooks Headers and ExhaustMagnuson SuperchargersMBRP PerformanceRange TechnologySDHQ Built Power Steering ReservoirsS&B FiltersS&B Filters | Chevy/GMCS&B Filters | FordS&B Filters | JeepS&B Filters | ToyotaVibrant PerformanceAir FiltersSafety Products PCI Safety ProductsImpact Racing Safety ProductsHead and Neck RestraintsPRP HarnessesPRP Harnesses AccessoriesCruzArmorCleaners and Hand SanitizerLucas Oil Hand Sanitizer 2qt-11175Hand Sanitizer 4oz.Molecule Hi-Performance CleanersSDHQ Built Products SDHQ Built Lighting ProductsA-Pillars Light MountsBehind the Grille Light MountsSDHQ Built Switch Pros MountsSDHQ Built FiberglassSDHQ Built Interior ProductsSDHQ Built Protection ProductsSDHQ Built ABS GuardsSDHQ Built SlidersSDHQ Built Skid PlatesSDHQ Built CV BootsSDHQ Built In Bed Chase RacksSDHQ Built Winch MountsSDHQ Built Switch Pros MountsSDHQ Built Power Steering ReservoirsSDHQ Built Electrical ProductsSDHQ StrapsSDHQ Tool BagsSDHQ Built Products Coming SoonSDHQ Swag SDHQ Mens T-ShirtsWomen’s T-ShirtsYouth T-ShirtsSDHQ MasksSDHQ General Use MaskSDHQ Outdoor Division TubeSDHQ Motorsports TubeSDHQ JacketsSDHQ HatsSDHQ Tank TopsSDHQ Stickers and DecalsHeatwave SunglassesSliders and Skid Plates SDHQ Built Billet ABS GuardsRCI Off RoadCBI Off RoadSDHQ Built SlidersSuspension Icon Vehicle DynamicsCamburg EngineeringCarli SuspensionEibach SpringsFox ShocksTotal Chaos FabricationKing Offroad ShocksDirt King FabricationLocked Off-Road | BumpstopsKryptonite SuspensionSDHQ Shock RebuildsDuroBumpsUpper Control ArmsIcon Vehicle Dynamics | Upper Control ArmsCamburg Engineering | Upper Control ArmsTotal Chaos Fabrication | Upper Control ArmsUpper Control Arm Uniball Replacement KitsTires BFG TiresToyo TiresPaddle Tires Tools Push Lock Hose ToolKoul Tools Hose Assembly and Fitting ToolsSDHQ Tool BagsAll German MotorsportsEarl's Performance Tools and FittingsSDISteel-It 1002 Polyurethane Anti-Rust AerosolMr. Gasket Tools3 In 1 Locking/ Twisting/ Wire CuttersHose Pinch Pliers57 PC Universal Tool Roll for Side by SidesTrail Gear Bubba RopeFactor 55PowerTankPro Eagle JacksMAXTRAX Recovery RampsStrapsSDHQ StrapsMac Tie DownsSpeedStrapsRotopax ContainersOff Road Spill KitAnvil Off-RoadUtility Jug w/ Filler HoseWheels Icon AlloysMethod Race WheelsKMC-XD Series WheelsRaceline Wheels Vorsteiner Venomrex Wheels
OMF Beauty Rings
UTV Spec Wheels Method 400 Series UTV WheelsIcon Alloys | UTV WheelsSplined Lug Nut KitWinches and Mounts Warn WinchesSDHQ Built Winch MountsWinch AccessoriesBubba RopeFactor 55Pro EagleBrowse by Vehicle Toyota '07-Current Toyota Tundra’16-Current Toyota Tacoma’10-Current Toyota 4Runner'08-Current Toyota 200 Series Land Cruiser'05-15 Toyota Tacoma'03-09 Toyota 4Runner'07-14 Toyota FJ CruiserFord '17-Current Ford Raptor'19-Current Ford Ranger'17-Current Ford F250/350'15-Current Ford F150'10-14 Ford Raptor'04-14 Ford F150'05-16 Ford F250/350Chevy/GMC '19-Current Chevy/GMC 1500'07-18 Chevy/GMC 1500'11-19 Chevy/GMC 2500/3500'01-10 Chevy/GMC 2500/3500Ram  '09-18 Ram 1500Dodge Ram 2500/3500Jeep '20-Current Jeep (JT) Gladiator'18-Current Jeep JL'07-17 Jeep JKSDHQ Build Gallery The SDHQ CollectionFordToyotaJeepChevy/GMCNissanRamContact Us Shock RebuildsOnline Order ReturnSDHQ Military DiscountSDHQ Law Enforcement DiscountContact UsSDHQ JobsSubmit Resell License (Tax Exempt) Info
Search
Home
Shop By Category
Brands
Browse by Vehicle
SDHQ Build Gallery
Contact Us
ABOUT US
Contact Us
Item added to cart. View cart and check out.
Close
Close
SDHQ Privacy Policy
SHIPPING POLICY:
Typically all orders are processed within 24 hours. If we discover a delay in your shipment, we will do our best to contact you right away.
You will notice that no shipping charges are shown during your check out process no matter what method of delivery you choose. We do this to allow you to receive to lowest shipping cost possible. In an effort to keep the cost of shipping down, we try to consolidate shipments, and use the most efficient method of shipping, whether it be freight or UPS ground services. The shipping charges will be determined by our shipping department and you will be notified of the cost. This is the best way for us to give you the lowest cost on shipping your product.
If you have special shipping requirements please contact our sales department. team@sdhqoffroad.com
PROCESSING YOUR ORDER:
After the shipping costs have been calculated, you will be sent an email with an updated link to your order. Your updated order will include your order's shipping costs and be your original order with the letter "A" at the end. While checking for updates on your order please add an "A" to the end of your order number, as your order number without the "A" will show canceled since it has been superseded.
FIBERGLASS SHIPPING POLICY
Our shipping department takes the same time and effort in packaging your products as our engineers do in designing them. However, damage can still occur in shipping. Most of these damaged items can be easily repaired during install and or in paint prep. If this is not the case, the buyer must inspect the packaging and the products carefully upon receiving them, then accept the shipment and if need be, notate any damages and irregularities, such as crushed, torn, punctured, or broken parts on both the packaging and the product, on the freight bill or receipt at the driver’s presence. A signed receipt without any notation releases the carrier as well as SDHQ from any further damage claim. Discovery of damages after a clear delivery becomes the responsibility of the customer.The buyer must notify SDHQ of any damages within 24 hours. In cases of damage with proper notion on receipt, the carrier will determine whether to pay for the repair cost or replacement value of the damaged goods after damage inspection. Replacement value is the amount the buyer paid to SDHQ and is not negotiable. All disputes about the settlement amount shall be addressed with the carrier. SDHQ, under no circumstances, shall be liable for the damaged product or for subsequent settlement of the claim with the carrier.
RETURNS:
We will not accept returns without prior authorization. Please fill out the SDHQ Online Order Return Form. Provide a specific reason for your return, and request a Return Goods Authorization (RGA) number.
SDHQ ONLINE ORDER RETURN FORM
When packaging your parts for shipping, write the RGA number on the outside packaging in large, easily visible letters, and include a copy of the original invoice in the package.
We strongly recommend packing any parts with fragile components with sufficient padding. Note that we are not responsible for products being returned to us that are damaged mid-shipment.
Return the package(s) freight prepaid to:
SUPERDUTY HQ
190 S McQueen RdSte 109. Gilbert, Arizona 85233
Items may be returned if unused within 30 days of shipping, with a 20% re-stocking fee. There are NO returns after 30 days from date of receipt. Freight is nonrefundable.
Refunds will be given on parts only and excludes labor or installation charges, shipping, or any other charges. All parts must be returned in the original package, cannot be damaged or installed, and must be in original condition. All returned parts must be sent freight prepaid and are subject to a re-boxing fee.
Certain parts are not returnable, including but not limited to Special Order parts, wheels and tires that have been mounted and/or installed, electrical items, and closeouts.
Customer returns for parts received as part of a "free shipping" or "shipping special" offer will be credited for the amount of the returned parts less actual outbound shipping charges paid by us and any restocking fee that may apply.
GIFT CARD POLICY:
Treat this card as cash. It will not be replaced if lost or stolen. This card is redeemable for merchandise only. Redeemable online or in store at SDHQ Motorsports
Terms of Use / Privacy Policy
Welcome to the web site ("Site") for Superduty HQ, LLC ("Superduty HQ, LLC ").
BY ACCESSING, BROWSING AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREED TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE ("TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE") INCLUDING THE PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY") (COLLECTIVELY THE "TERMS") AND TO COMPLY WITH ALL APPLICABLE U.S. LAWS AND REGULATIONS. In addition, you hereby represent and certify that you are at least eighteen (18) years of age. If you do not or cannot agree to the Terms, you are not authorized to use the Site or any of the services offered through the Site. Superduty HQ, LLC reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to update, revise, supplement and to otherwise modify these Terms, and to impose new or additional terms and conditions on your use of the Site from time to time. Such updates, revisions, supplements, modifications and additional rules, policies, terms and conditions (collectively referred to in these Terms as "Additional Terms") shall be effective immediately and incorporated into these Terms upon notice thereof, which may be given by any reasonable means including by posting to the Site. Your continued viewing or use of the Site following such notice shall be deemed to conclusively indicate your acceptance of any and all such Additional Terms.
ACCEPTABLE USE OF THE SITE.In order to use the Site, you must obtain access to the Internet and pay any and all service fees associated with such access.
(a) Individual Use. You agree that you are only authorized to visit, view and to retain a single copy of pages of the Site for your own internal use and not on behalf of any other person or entities, and that you shall not duplicate, download, publish, modify or otherwise distribute any material on the Site for any purpose other than for your own internal use unless otherwise specifically authorized by Superduty HQ, LLC in writing.
(b) Deep Links; Linking. You agree not to "deep-link" to the Site, meaning that you shall not create, post, display, publish or distribute any link to any page other than the front (home) page of the Site for any purpose, unless specifically authorized by Superduty HQ, LLC in writing to do so. If you do want to link to the Site in any manner, you may contact the Superduty HQ, LLC Webmaster at info@superdutyheadquarters.com to seek approval.
(c) Framing. You agree not to create any frames at any other web sites pertaining to or using any of the content located at the Site for any purpose, unless specifically authorized by Superduty HQ, LLC in writing to do so.
(d) Security, Cracking and Hacking. You are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the Site. Accordingly, you agree not to: (i) access data or materials not intended for you; (ii) log into a server or account which you are not authorized to access; (iii) attempt to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorization; or (iv) attempt to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including without limitation, by means of submitting a virus to the Site, overloading, "flooding", "mailbombing" or "crashing" the Site. Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability. Superduty HQ, LLC reserves the right to investigate occurrences which may involve such violations and may involve, and cooperate with, law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who have participated in such violations. You understand that data and communications, including e-mail and other electronic communications, may be accessed by unauthorized third parties when communicated over the Internet.
(e) You Are Responsible For All of Your Activities and All of The Content You Post or Submit. You represent and warrant that any information and/or material you post or provide to Superduty HQ, LLC by means of the Site, including, without limitation, as part of any registration or subscription or to gain access to or use any services offered on the Site ("Submissions"), is truthful, accurate, not misleading, not confidential property of others, not in violation of any other third party's rights and offered in good faith. You agree NOT to use the Site for or in connection with any of the following activities: (i) transmitting or relaying spam, spoofing or otherwise impersonating any person or entity, or falsely stating or otherwise misrepresenting your identity or affiliation in any way; (ii) using the Site for any fraudulent or illegal purpose; (iii) e-mailing, uploading, or otherwise transmitting or using the Site in furtherance of the use, distribution or transmission of any unlawful, harassing, defamatory, tortious, libelous, sexually explicit, obscene, hateful, racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind; and (iv) transmitting material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots or other computer programming routines or engines that are intended to damage, destroy, disrupt or otherwise impair a computer's functionality or the operation of the Site.
(f) Information Disclosed via the Site. IN ADDITION TO ANY OTHER WARRANTY DISCLAIMER PROVIDED IN THESE TERMS, ANY INFORMATION DISCLOSED TO YOU VIA THE SITE INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY CONTENT, PERSONAL OR PROFESSIONAL RECOMMENDATIONS, PRODUCT RECOMMENDATIONS, PRODUCT DESCRIPTIONS, PRODUCT SAFETY AND/OR EFFECTIVENESS MATERIALS, ARE NOT OFFERED WITH ANY WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION AS TO ABILITY, ACCURACY, PERFORMANCE OR SUITABILITY FOR YOUR INTENDED PURPOSE OR COMPLIANCE WITH APPLICABLE LAW. Superduty HQ, LLC ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY, AND DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY FOR, ANY ILLNESS OR INJURY RESULTING FROM USING ANY PRODUCTS OR FOLLOWING ANY ADVICE CONTAINED ON THIS SITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT USE OF ANY PRODUCT INVOLVES UNFORESEEABLE RISKS AND UNCERTAINTIES.
(g) Do Not Violate Third Party Intellectual Property Rights. Without limiting the foregoing, you shall not, and by using the Site you agree not to, use the Site to: (i) transmit or post any Submissions that are copyrighted, unless you are the copyright owner or have obtained the permission of the copyright owner to transmit it; (ii) transmit or post any Submissions that reveal trade secrets, unless you own them or have the permission of the owner to so transmit them; or (iii) transmit or post any Submissions that infringe on any Intellectual Property Rights (as defined below) of others or violates the privacy or rights of publicity of others. Furthermore, unless otherwise expressly provided, you acknowledge and agree that: (a) all Submissions shall become property of Superduty HQ, LLC; (b) Superduty HQ, LLC has the right to publish the Submissions for any type of use including for promotional and advertising purposes, in accordance with the terms set forth in the Privacy Policy, without compensation to you of any kind; (c) any Submissions that you submit to any part of the Site are non-confidential for all purposes; and (d) that if you make any such Submission, you automatically grant, represent and warrant that the owner of such content has expressly granted Superduty HQ, LLC a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, world-wide exclusive license to use the Submissions in any manner, media or form now known or hereafter developed. Superduty HQ, LLC shall have the right to sublicense its rights. The term "Intellectual Property Rights" shall mean, collectively, rights under patent, trademark, copyright and trade secret laws, and any other intellectual property or proprietary rights recognized in any country or jurisdiction worldwide, including, without limitation, moral rights and similar rights.
(h) Ownership. Superduty HQ, LLC puts a lot of content on the Site for you to examine from time to time including, without limitation, text, graphics, photographs, pictures, drawings, animation, audio, video, literature and any other material distributed by Superduty HQ, LLC on, through or in connection with the Site. Moreover, Superduty HQ, LLC attempts to display the content in a way that will be easily accessible and useful for you, the user. All content and materials on the Site including, without limitation, text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips and software included in the Site and any services offered on the Site, are the property of Superduty HQ, LLC, its sponsors or business affiliates, and/or their respective licensors, and are subject to U.S. and international Intellectual Property Rights laws. The compilation of all content on the Site is the exclusive property of Superduty HQ, LLC and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on the Site is the property of Superduty HQ, LLC or its licensors and is subject to U.S. and international copyright laws. Except to the minimum extent otherwise expressly permitted under copyright law, no copying or exploitation of material from the Site is permitted except expressly in accordance with these Terms or with the express written permission of Superduty HQ, LLC and any other applicable copyright owner. You acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by virtue of downloading copyrighted material from the Site. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are expressly reserved to Superduty HQ, LLC.
(i) Distribution Rights and Citations. Superduty HQ, LLC cites content; including but not limited to; images, product descriptions, various materials relating to the use, installation, and handling of respective products sold by Superduty HQ, LLC . This content is the property of the respective Manufacturer for which Superduty HQ, LLC is an authorized distributor. Said content is owned and managed by the contextually referenced Manufacturer and therefore any sourced content used by Superduty HQ, LLC is UNALTERED, this only relates as the facts provided by the referenced Manufacturer remains unedited by Superduty HQ, LLC , however this does not negate any restructuring of said content.
WARRANTY DISCLAIMER.THE CONTENT, SERVICES, INFORMATION AND ACCESS TO THE SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, SATISFACTORY QUALITY AND NONINFRINGEMENT. Superduty HQ, LLC DOES NOT WARRANT THAT ANY PART OF THE SITE WILL OPERATE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR?FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS OR THAT TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM THE SITE AND ACCESS TO THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, CONTINUOUS OR ERROR-FREE. Superduty HQ, LLC DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE SITE IN TERMS OF ITS QUALITY, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. YOU SHOULD THEREFORE VERIFY ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM THE SITE BEFORE ACTING ON IT.
EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED, Superduty HQ, LLC EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, CONTENT, AVAILABILITY OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, SERVICES OR MERCHANDISE FOUND ON THIRD PARTY SITES THAT LINK TO OR FROM THE SITE. Superduty HQ, LLC DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR PRODUCT OR SERVICE ORDERING FUNCTIONS, ORDER FULFILLMENT OR COMPLIANCE OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WITH ANY MANUFACTURER'S WARRANTIES OR SPECIFICATIONS. Superduty HQ, LLC CANNOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR THE MATERIAL CONTAINED ON THIRD PARTY SITES AND/OR RELATED SERVICES NOR DOES Superduty HQ, LLC MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION YOU MIGHT BE REQUESTED TO GIVE TO THIRD PARTY SITES.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. TO THE FURTHEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, Superduty HQ, LLC NEGLIGENCE, SHALL Superduty HQ, LLC, ITS AFFILIATES, RELATED ENTITIES, VENDORS OR CONTENT PROVIDERS, BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY AND/OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, ANY CONTENT AND/OR ANY RELATED SOFTWARE, EVEN IF Superduty HQ, LLC OR AN AUTHORIZED Superduty HQ, LLC REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING ELSE CONTAINED IN THESE TERMS, IN THE EVENT THE TERMS OF THIS SECTION, OR ANY PART OF THIS SECTION, SHALL BE HELD INVALID OR UNENFORCEABLE BY A COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION, IN NO EVENT SHALL Superduty HQ, LLC 'S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU, OR ANYONE CLAIMING BY OR THROUGH YOU, FOR ANY DAMAGES, LOSSES, CLAIMS AND/OR CAUSES OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE, SHALL EXCEED HALF OF THE INITAIL ORDER.
Accuracy of Content and Pricing Information:Because prices, product descriptions and availability can change quickly, Superduty HQ, LLC does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the information provided on the Site. Also, Superduty HQ, LLC may make changes to the information contained herein, including to the products and prices described in the site, at any time, without prior notice to you (including after you have submitted your order). Information at this Site is periodically updated, but it may not be current or complete at the moment you visit this Site and may contain errors or inaccuracies. In no event shall Superduty HQ, LLC or its service or product providers be liable to you in any manner whatsoever for any decision made by you, or for any act or failure to act by you, in reliance upon information provided at this Site. If a product you purchase does not match the description on the Site, as your sole and exclusive remedy you may return the product, unused, to Superduty HQ, LLC and receive a refund (please see shipping page for Return Requirements) of your purchase price. Items in your shopping cart will reflect the most recent price displayed on the items product detail page. Prices are frequently updated to adjust for different sales, limited pricing, and other discounting. Therefore, prices on the product detail page and in your cart may change after such updates to reflect the current prices. Placing items in your cart does not reserve the current prices shown at that time, and prices are reserved only by placing an order. From time to time, despite our efforts, a small number of the items in our catalog may be mispriced. Please note that such errors or inaccuracies may be related to product descriptions, pricing and availability. In the event of a pricing error, Superduty HQ, LLC will take one of the following options: (1) If an items correct price is lower than our stated price, we will charge the lower amount and ship you the item; or (2) if an items correct price is higher than our stated price, we will, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions before shipping or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation. We apologize for any inconvenience. If you are not satisfied with your purchase due to any errors or inaccuracies, you may return it in accordance with our return procedure. Discounts are limited-time offers and are not valid with other offers. For shipping, cancellation, and other ordering questions, please refer to our Shipping & Returns page.
INDEMNIFICATION You shall indemnify, defend and hold harmless Superduty HQ, LLC and its sponsors, business affiliates, vendors, content providers, subsidiaries, related entities, affiliates, officers, directors, employees, attorneys and agents, from and against any and all damages, claims and actions brought by you or any third party resulting from your use of the site in violation of these terms or the infringement by you of any intellectual property rights of any person or entity.
GOVERNING LAW AND ARBITRATION.The laws of the State of Arizona (excluding any principles of conflicts of laws) govern your use of the Site, the services and these Terms. You agree that the parties shall settle any claim or dispute relating to these Terms by binding arbitration in Arizona under the Commercial Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under these Terms shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to these Terms, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise. NOTWITHSTANDING THE DISPUTE RESOLUTION REQUIREMENTS SET FORTH ABOVE, FOR ANY INJUNCTIVE RELIEF RELATING TO YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, RELATED SERVICES, YOU AGREE AND HEREBY SUBMIT TO THE EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION AND VENUE OF THE APPROPRIATE STATE OR FEDERAL COURTS LOCATED IN MARICOPA COUNTY, ARIZONA, U.S.A.
WAIVER AND SEVERABILITY.Furthermore, no delay or omission by Superduty HQ, LLC to exercise any right or any noncompliance on your part with respect to the Terms shall impair any such right or be construed to be a waiver by Superduty HQ, LLC. If any provision of the Terms is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable in whole or in part, such provision shall, as to such jurisdiction, be ineffective to the extent of such invalidity or unenforceability without in any manner affecting the validity or enforceability thereof in any other jurisdiction or the remaining provisions hereof in any jurisdiction, provided, however, if such invalid or unenforceable provision may be modified so as to be valid and enforceable as a matter of law, such provision will be deemed to have been modified so as to be valid and enforceable to the maximum extent permitted by law.
CONTRACT ELECTRONICALLYYou agree that the Terms, combined with your act of using the Site and/or the services offered on or through the Site have the same legal force and effect as a written contract with your written signature and satisfy any laws that require a writing or signature, including any applicable Statute of Frauds. You further agree that you shall not challenge the validity, enforceability or admissibility of the Terms on the grounds that it was electronically transmitted or authorized. In addition, you acknowledge that you have had the opportunity to print the Terms.
Information Gathered through the Superduty HQ, LLC Sites:
Superduty HQ, LLC will track the domains from which people visit the Superduty HQ, LLC Sites in order to gain aggregate data that may be analyzed for trends and statistics. Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, Superduty HQ, LLC may use accumulated aggregate data for several purposes including, but not limited to, marketing analysis, evaluation of Superduty HQ, LLC 's services, and business planning.
Currently, Superduty HQ, LLC uses personal information as a basis for notifications to users, and in order to implement the Terms and Conditions of Use governing the Superduty HQ, LLC Sites (the "Terms"). Generally, the user names, email addresses, and any additional information that a user may choose to post are publicly available on the Superduty HQ, LLC Sites. When users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information that may contain Registration Data, as defined in the Terms, or otherwise post personal information in conjunction with content subject to a license, such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the terms of the applicable license. An example of such a disclosure includes, but is not limited to, a user's disclosure of personal information as part of a message posted to a public message forum, or a publicly released software application.
Superduty HQ, LLC may conduct surveys or other studies of its user base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option, but Superduty HQ, LLC does reserve the right to conduct mandatory surveys in the future. With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and Superduty HQ, LLC will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where Superduty HQ, LLC advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, Superduty HQ, LLC reserves the right to disclose text information provided by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed. Circumstances under which Superduty HQ, LLC would publicly disclose aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population, providing data to Superduty HQ, LLC advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, business planning, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications.
Cookies: Superduty HQ, LLC employs "cookies" to provide users with tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that a website, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser which, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory. Superduty HQ, LLC uses cookies to better serve users of our Superduty HQ, LLC Sites; any cookies sent by Superduty HQ, LLC will be marked so that they will be accessible only by Superduty HQ, LLC . All Superduty HQ, LLC sites are subject to this Privacy Statement. However, at his or her option and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.
Other Notification: In order to implement or enforce the Terms, Superduty HQ, LLC may use user-provided e-mail addresses to contact users on an individual basis. At no time, unless such disclosure is required by law, a governmental agency, or specifically authorized by the user, will Superduty HQ, LLC disclose individual user personal information to unrelated third parties that is not publicly available.
Links with other sites
The Superduty HQ, LLC Sites may contain links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by Superduty HQ, LLC 's affiliates, or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of the Superduty HQ, LLC Sites. Superduty HQ, LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit.
"Opt-in" Emails: Users may "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters, or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions.
Profile Display: In some cases, users' personal information may be publicly available through a user's profile display. In such cases, users have the option to opt out of publicly displaying their personal information, including e-mail addresses. Users may also enlist this technique when posing comments on certain OSDN Sites. In cases where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at the user's discretion and may be changed at any time by the user.
Email Display: In some cases, users may have the opportunity to use an Superduty HQ, LLC Site to send electronic mail to another user or email list. In such cases, a user's valid email address and real name will be included with such messages. In order to prevent abuse, users may not opt-out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from using such Superduty HQ, LLC Site to transmit an email message.
Security
To secure site integrity, Superduty HQ, LLC employs measures, including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures.
Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis.
Enforcement
In the event that Superduty HQ, LLC becomes aware that site security is compromised or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, Superduty HQ, LLC shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Privacy Statement.
If Superduty HQ, LLC becomes aware that a user's personal information provided to Superduty HQ, LLC has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Statement, Superduty HQ, LLC shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that Superduty HQ, LLC knows this information.
No Guarantees For Factors Beyond Superduty HQ, LLC's Control
While this Privacy Statement expresses Superduty HQ, LLC 's standards for maintenance of private data, it is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond Superduty HQ, LLC 's control (e.g., "script kiddies", "hacking", "crackers and other malcontents") that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, Superduty HQ, LLC disclaims any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of private information.
ATTN: STATE OF CALIFORNIA CONSUMERS WARNING: Some products may contain chemicals such as DEHP, which can cause cancer, birth defects or other reproductive harm. Learn More
Follow us
Facebook
Instagram
YouTube
Company Info
About Us
The SDHQ Collection
Contact Us
Shock Rebuilds
Become a dealer
SDHQ Jobs
Online Order Return
Policies
Sign Up for our Newsletter
SDHQ has continued to raise the standard of what an off-road shop should be. SDHQ bases its principles around a strong commitment to customer service, quality products, competitive prices, and professional installation. The backbone of our company is our talented team of knowledgeable staff that each truly shares our customers' passion.
Subscribe
Store Hours
Monday-Friday: 8:00am-5:00pm
Saturday:
9:00am-2:00pm
Sunday: Closed
190 S McQueen Rd
Ste 109. Gilbert, Arizona
© 2020, SDHQ.
SDHQ Privacy Policy
Skip to content
